tutlane.com 2018-03-26

# Terms and Conditions, Privacy Policy, Terms of Use | Tutlane - Tutlane

Tutlane Services Private Limited ("Tutlane," the "Company," "we," "us," and "our,") respect your privacy and are committed to protecting your right to privacy as a user of our website. We have made every effort to ensure your information is secure. This privacy policy information covers what information is collected, what we do with it, and what you can do about it. You can use this information to make your decisions about your privacy.

### Information collected by Tutlane

We collect and store the information that you voluntarily disclose to us, in order to access our free tutorials, courses, articles and discussion forum and we will never be sold, exchanged or disclosed to any third party for marketing purposes. You can browse our website without registration and you can opt to receive offers from us and you have total control on the privacy of your information.

We may use your information to contact you via email or telephone, typically to get feedback, to inform you about new products or provide support on your issues. If you do not want us to contact you via email, you can unsubscribe at any time.

### Cookie Information

In order to enhance your online experience and track website performance, our website uses cookies. It's a small text file which gets placed in your computer hard drive and can be retrieved later. Cookies do not tell us who you are.

### External Links

Our website may have links to other sites, which include third party websites or resources. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and information practices of third party websites. Please read the privacy policies of third party websites as every website has different terms of use and privacy policies.

### Course Content

Course content for all the study programs both online and blended programs, is provided only for the purpose of education and guidance. The course content is reviewed regularly and is subject to change without notice. Tutlane reserves the right to modify training content without notice.

### Copyright information

You can electronically copy or take print outs of the website pages, only for personal use. Tutlane holds the copyright to all the material on this website, unless otherwise indicated. A written permission from the copyright holder must be obtained for any use of this material other than for purposes permitted by law.

### Personal Information Corrections

You can contact us if you notice that the information we are holding is incorrect or incomplete. Please send us an email at [support@tutlane.com](mailto:support@tutlane.com)

### Changes to Privacy Policy

These privacy policy terms may change time to time and we reserve the right to change the terms of the privacy policy at any time. When we update the privacy policy, all our registered users will be notified via email.

### Privacy Policy Questions?

If you have any questions regarding Tutlane Privacy Policy, you may email to [support@tutlane.com](mailto:support@tutlane.com), or write at the following address

  * __**Address:** No.116, New Market Street, Choolaimedu High Road, Chennai, Tamilnadu - 600094
  * __**Phone:** (+91) - 9025657705
  * __**Email:** [support@tutlane.com](mailto:support@tutlane.com)
